There's a path I chose for everyone in
life, but I think my arm is already
chiselled out for me.
Realistically, I shouldn't be here.
I've been kidnapped running a boot.
50 grand on my head, 100 grand on my head.
What the fuck have I been doing for the
last five or ten years?
People are being shot.
They get blasted in the legs.
They get petrol poured over them.
They get set on fire.
10k, 50 grand a key is a lot of money.
People can go missing for that money.
Bump and they're gone.
Push comes to shove.
I'm here to collect money, that's what I
do.
And that's what I've got.
Ten years ago, Sean Smith was fighting a
war against the rival drug gang.
To win, he introduced urban terrorism to
the British underworld.
Victims were firebombed with homemade
napalm, attacked with grenades and sprayed
up with machine guns.
In retaliation, his enemies tried to blow
Sean up with a car bomb, the biggest
explosion on mainland Britain between the
fall of the
IRA and 7-7.
Sean Smith was known as an enforcer.
Today, after five years in prison, he is
trying to modify those skills by working
as a debt collector in the straight-going
economy.
I think if I took on every job that people
offer you, I'd be dead in 12 months.
I value life too much.
Yeah,
bro.
I've always been out.
Declets and pubs, violence.
You call it enforced, I call it being
mediated.
I don't give a fuck of anyone else.
I stand up against anyone.
The ones going on, I haven't gone.
Every man's only got the same.
It's who wants it the most, and I want it
the most.
It's not how big the dog is, it's how big
the fight is in the dog, and I won't
fucking stop.
That's it.
These are some of the lads that are on
homestead with me.
I can see the big fan of the camp up.
And yeah, you don't want them knocking on
your door or that thing before the
morning.
Even when you do fucking smile.
All the jokes when you smile.
Looks like a boat down to you to watch.
What we're doing here today is a skip
yard.
My mate got in a bother and was away for a
couple of months.
The fella's seen an opportunity to go, but
they don't have to pay him rent, he's not
here.
That's the way some people are.
And he's ran up a death.
He knew my mate was about to come out of
jail and he's basically filled the yard
with
contaminated waste.
The varmint I held put a 300 grand bill on
it, so he moved it, 300,000 to the roll of
money.
So I'm hoping we can sort this out.
Show you that.
All these little areas in sight, this is
like our bread and butter, my bread and
butter.
These are all working class people, little
companies here, little welding, painters,
garages.
I do work for most of these around here.
The way the economy is now, the country is
on its arse.
But these people aren't fighters or so
they're in ghosts and we come and collect
it for them.
But they all get to know us because we've
got the gym and we're local.
You know there's always, you know, if they
want like 10 or 15 men within 10 minutes,
they can have that in 10 minutes.
You know, you can't really get that
anywhere.
We always make sure there's good strong
lads behind us.
Ah, it's this one.
Yeah,
it is this one.
Yo Tom.
Hiya mate, I'm at your yard now.
Fucking hell mate, what's all this?
Jesus Christ What I'm gonna do, we're
gonna...
I'm just having a look in the cabin if
there's anything here.
We're gonna fuck off.
Mikey's gonna sit on this tonight in case
anyone comes back and forth.
And then we can just nab it.
We'll just nab whoever it is then.
Look at that what they've got by the door
there.
Fucking blade.
Tommy, just tell us where he is mate.
Just give me a door to knock on and I'll
do it.
So we want 25 grand off him up front and
pay the rest off.
And me and Mikey can collect it.
You happy with that?
Sound.
Go on then.
Often, Sean's debts fall into the grey
area between the legitimate economy and
the underworld.
A lucrative market potentially worth £150
billion in Britain.
This is a typical death for Sean.
A dispute between a businessman and a
gangster over £300,000.
To recover the debt, Sean has brought
backup and a dog unit.
But just in case things get out of
control, off camera there is a notorious
gangster with a history of firearms and
extreme
violence.
We don't know him, our mate knows him.
He will know who we are after tonight.
We're just going to go to his house now,
see if we can have hold of him.
It might just be a plug with him being in
a cheap car.
Having a flat, he might just have that for
his mail.
Do you know what I mean?
He might just check his mail, then fuck
back off to where he's got his beer and
his kids.
Because we'll just knock on the door and
say, have you seen Andy?
If they say yes, then that's it.
Game over.
Just press every buzzer.
I know.
I'm not going to wait till they come up
with a guy
calling.
It's my new night of nature.
Is it?
It's got a silver e-horse.
I'm going to get some
kids to park up here and just watch it.
But I've only got to come in that way.
If one of you just parks up tonight, I'll
just wait for them.
I'm probably just going to hide out
places.
You know, some debts you can ring up, you
can make a phone call, get paid.
Some debts you turn up and before you know
it, it's all over now, and before they go,
a gang of idiots.
This one is just, it's a waiting game.
He's obviously having a good time with
someone else's money, but that time will
run out.
As soon as it does, here's the knock.
This fella you're going to see on the
celly now is the local fucking bully.
He stabbed a pregnant woman, battered a
half-fella 71.
I knocked him out last year, broke his
jaw, knocked six teeth out, put him in
hospital.
And he stayed away for a year and now he
is trying to come back.
I got more pissed off that he interrupted
me reading me Bernard Hopkins fucking
article.
Still not finished that?
People love trying to come in here and
just come down for a cup of tea.
You know, or a chat, you know, even at the
train.
You know, and they'll sit there like old
grannies, some of them.
You know, they all go round the corner
drinking tea and just gamming, you know.
Did you watch Connie last night?
No.
Oh mate, you fucking boss No, it's not
only a son.
It's not only a son.
It's not a son at all.
It's my life.
Son of a bitch, that's been a bad son of a
bitch.
Your life, my life.
It's like a community centre really.
It's done a lot for people actually.
You know, it's kept me strong a few times
as well.
I help a lot of them out.
It's like the kid who got sections and
he's just come out today.
He is a boss, boss kid and a top promising
boxer.
You come out of the winnock after being in
sections, you just come right here to see
me.
One for work and two to tie them.
He's got out I never bought a one and a
half.
He's got a little bit of your anger.
Yeah.
I'll fuck him up.
Yeah, you know.
Right.
He's got out.
Yeah.
We'll get him.
I told him to run.
He'll just smash him.
He's not going nowhere, is he?
No, that's what I mean.
He'll go nowhere after the jump.
And when he went, you know what I mean?
So we'll get him.
I told him to run.
He's not fucking up under us.
Yeah.
He's got money.
Yeah, I've got a bipolar personality
disorder, bipolar and violent tendencies.
So, but if it weren't for Sean, I'd
probably be paying myself.
Because I self, as you can see, self-amp.
I stabbed myself, cut myself.
You can see my rib when I take that off.
So can you tell us about what was the
situation like?
A woman.
A woman winding me up.
How did I do it?
God, I just looked in and ripped it.
I had under a native Allium as well, so I
took an overdose at the same time.
So that's when he put me in the Allings
Park, which is Warrington's nut
house.
But like I say, Sian keeps me up straight
and lather.
He says if we do it again he's gonna knock
me out so I think that's enough.
Come on, Work,
Come on, try and fucking throw me in this.
We are there for him all the time.
He's done it before on his face, on his
neck, on his wrist.
And we are gonna help him get him through
this because he is a top, top kid.
And his talent is unbelievable.
It's just that he's, the problems he's
had.
When I was 10 to 11 I was sexually abused
by a lad that my mum used to foster.
And I felt like I wasn't a man for years.
And that's why I took up boxing, street
fighting, mixed martial arts, to prove
to myself that I'm a man.
You know, instead of feeling weak and
vulnerable like that lad made me feel.
And every time I fight I picture his face.
I remember standing there looking in the
mirror thinking I fucking hate you I want
you dead
and I just got a blade and I cut myself
and then I felt better I didn't hate
myself no more
so I wasn't taking the drugs as much so
when I fell down I was cutting myself
I ain't got no more room anyway to cut
myself now, so I don't think I'll be
carrying on doing it.
What the fuck's that?
You can't do bodies, pal.
No.
I'm just fucking done.
Fucking idiot.
Have you?
No, get your hands off me.
Let's go.
Have you got some?
No, I couldn't fucking pass it on the
ground.
I fucking should have.
I'll tell you what I'll do, the next time
you do it, mate, I'll buy you from the
gym.
I mean it.
I mean it, patience.
Patience, mate.
Go on, get in.
See you later.
See you later, man.
Go, Red That's right, Red Come on, come on
Come on, James, Red That's finished Come
on, go, Red
Sexual abuse is an unspeakable taboo in
the underworld.
However, male rape is commonly used as a
weapon by gangsters to enforce a debt.
This is a less well-known form of
underworld violence, which acts as a
powerful propaganda tool over and above
the physical
and mental suffering it causes.
I went with these two older fellas, proper
hard case fellas, one adult two metres.
And he went, come here, he's collecting
the debt.
I could have a little bash him, you know.
I'd have a go with anyone.
I said, yeah, come on.
They go, I'm like, go and have a look
around the house, go and have a look
upstairs.
I goes upstairs, just having a mooch.
She's any money, any duty.
All right, I'm looking around, neck and
neck and head.
Go on, John, go on, go on What's going on
there?
Comes down, here's Don, this fella who's
like, showing me how to do doors, respects
everyone.
Dead respectful, dead courteous with his
band, his kids, but a very wicked, not,
I wouldn't say evil, wicked, you know what
I mean?
He couldn't really fight, but he was dead,
dead wicked.
And they've got him over this table, and
he's fucking shagging this fella up the
ass.
And the other fella is taking pictures.
I went, whoa, whoa, what's going on?
He went, Sean, Sean, just shut up.
Just watch.
I went, hang on John, John Lee.
He went, leave it, leave it, Lane.
Watch him Lane son, watch him Lane.
Left him a little note, he fucked off,
there's a little note there, pay, and a
picture.
They ring him back up, you know what's
just happened, we want the fucking door
within a couple of weeks.
These pictures will get put everywhere,
your credibility's gone, and we'll tell
everyone you're a faggot.
I went, why can't we just fucking pay
them?
Break something.
He went, he's used to that John, he's like
one of us.
He'll stand and have a go.
Two weeks after the fella's paid.
But six months after that, Brim, the
fucking fella hung himself.
He couldn't live with it.
I've gone a few angles.
Yeah, he couldn't live with it.
The shame.
He'll fight fever for you.
He said, that fella can have a go.
We go there and give him a pacer.
He'll pay someone to come and give one of
us a pacer.
And that's the way it'll go on.
He said, take everything away from him.
I've got a jet here for a very good friend
of mine who trains at a gym called Jaddy.
So we just want to chase him down today,
see, and see if we can get him.
Because he's a bit of a rat.
Well, he's a fucking cock-a-lote, isn't
he?
See, this one does your fucking head in.
He spent half an evening around people.
Yeah, what exactly happened was, this chap
who owed me the debt was originally a
partner
with my daughter.
They were going to get married, they
bought a property, they were getting a
property together, etc.
We thought he was smashing, but
unbeknownst to us, he was not nice to our
daughter.
We don't like people who profess to be
something and they're not be something
else.
We don't want people to be nice to us or
to members of our family and then they're
not nice behind our backs.
What that is, it's called bullying.
I'm not a nasty person.
I'm not six foot three and bulletproof.
But when I found out what he'd done, I
felt like smashing him to pieces.
He slapped my daughter, he hit her, and if
I could have got hold of him, I'd have
strangled him.
But I'm glad I didn't.
And I'm glad that there was somebody like
Sean who sat me down and said to me, Phil,
never do anything in anger.
You've got to do everything legal and
above board.
Well we've just found him on a site on the
internet with a picture of him.
So we're going to take a picture of that
just so we've got him.
Now he was ashamed.
So he began to call tomorrow.
Yeah, first one in a couple of months I've
not worn a
balaclava.
This guy we're going to see now has no
idea.
He's owed his death from last year.
But Nat and Tony know him.
It's come out, they know him fairly well.
So I'm initially going to go in and speak
to him.
I'll tell him how it is, what he's got to
pay, why I'm here.
Don't fuck with me, you don't need to know
who I am.
You know, I don't want this lad to lose
his job.
Even though he's a fucking rat as far as
I'm concerned, but you know I'm not a
cunt.
I want to pull him and tell him how it is
and it's got to be paid.
You can just tell me I'm a friend.
It's a good day for me, it's a bad day for
you.
You know Nat and Tony, don't you?
I'm a debt collector, I collect debts.
Charlie's a good friend of mine.
You said you'll honour that, you said
you'll pay it, and you haven't.
So basically we come and you're taking a
piss.
And Charlie's a fucking tough fella.
As long as we come to an agreement today.
Right That it gets paid, it gets paid Okay
If it's not, I fuck off and them two speak
to you Right, okay
If you wanna know who I am, don't fucking
google me No, no, no, it's okay I didn't
know a ginger lad could go even whiter
See?
Mate, he shook me hand, fucking sweating
buckets So it's a good day.
One, he'll pay.
Two, he's going to pay us a drink for
coming down.
So we're happy.
Chaddy just walks out with a grin on his
face.
To me, it's another job.
I am very happy for him.
But there's loads of people like that
everywhere.
And people need to just stand up to people
like this.
Because there's people like me everywhere.
It's not just me.
There'll always be a debt collector.
Someone will always owe someone.
People go to courts, courts are like debt
collectors are they?
Get divorced, I want my kitchen suite, I
want the car, I want this.
Before people do that they come to us.
We're cheaper and we'll probably get the
job done quicker.
Basically what's happened today, an
employee who I have, that I've only had
for a couple of months.
I gave him a job on a trial.
He's done well.
He's not a bad kid.
He is a good kid actually.
I've had rumours he's been selling juice
in the gym, which we just don't want to
buy a bike.
There is lads in here that do use
steroids, but they use it in their house.
And what they do with behind closed doors
is none of my business.
I'm not into that crap.
It's nothing to do with me.
There was another lad in here with a
tattoo on his head.
Not totally upstairs, it's a different
lad.
And I've looked after this kid for like
four or five months.
They can either have a dig or they can
admit what they've done, pay me a bit of
profit back, still tighten in the gym.
If they do that here, the two of them are
going to get a crack and that's it.
A couple of things I want to bring up.
This is not, I'm not fucking about.
I'm fucking dead dead serious here.
Right?
Really fucking dead serious.
You know me, I don't give shit, I don't
take shit.
Here's how serious I want to be.
I've been selling fucking gear in my
fucking gym, you cheeky twat.
You might have to go, I'm going.
Don't fucking lie to me.
You have been giving him gear and I'm
shocked at you for selling fucking gear.
I'm not selling anything.
Since what?
Since yesterday?
Since you said.
No, since you said.
You were selling it from the fucking
house.
Now you've been selling it from here.
I said I'd back you up Stu.
Yeah you did.
I said I'd back you up that's him.
Fucking forget about the camera.
This is business mate.
This is fucking business.
Only that I know Chaddy and he's related
to you Chaddy.
I will fucking flatten you mate.
Put you on the floor.
Right?
But I know you're going to need me to work
with you with that prick.
Normally he gets it off you though.
So from my point of view, he's buying off
you.
You're giving it to him.
You sell it in my gym.
What?
What do I do?
I might as well bend over then.
Come on, we have a go at that.
It's not business is it?
No, I understand that John.
It's not business.
You've made money, you've made money.
I've earned fuck all.
So here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna tax you a grand.
Give me a grand, keep your job, stay in
the gym.
If you don't want to give me a grand, by
the end of the day, I'll smash your head
in.
I'll smash your head in.
What do you want to do?
Simple as that.
What's up?
Right, hold your head up.
We'll sort it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Come on now, I've got to come up to you.
Come on.
That just had to be done with just a
little bit slap.
It is only a bit slap.
but they've made money in my business.
You've made money in this Jim?
So I want it.
I've got bills here.
I owe rent, I owe lecky, I owe everything
else.
I'm not a fucking millionaire.
Business is business.
But it's worked.
And that's the way we do work.
He's been right to that man, everything
goes through him.
And he's told me.
Because he's been right to that man.
He's not a fucking snitch.
If I see something going on, I tell him.
But I don't know about this.
He's my best mate.
It's called loyalty.
You can't buy it.
He's like, we got him, man.
We're fucking loyal as fuck.
That's the way it goes.
Nothing wrong has happened, like nothing
was done wrong, it was just lack of
communication really.
Sean, he'll help you out, he'll go to end
of earth for you.
But the minute that you think that you
cross him, bad move.
Don't really want to because I know who he
is.
I'd rather work with him than against him.
I have to now pay him about £500.
It's only fair really.
Here's his gym.
Can't argue with that really.
Everything goes through Sean, basically.
The lads know they've got off lightly with
telling off because a slap is nothing
compared to the extremist tendencies Sean
was
capable of in the past
Be ready to tell you what I've told but
like what I've done to people in my eyes
that you say they I wanted fucking Don't
to me
And yeah, of course, I don't sleep.
I'm on like 150 milliseries, 80 milligram
of propranolol, 7.5 milligram of zoprocon,
I have barotrophicus, which is a
pre-cancerous disease in my throat.
I have a tumour on my liver.
I'm waiting to go in and get a have a
knock on my stomach now that I'm eating my
polyp.
So I'm a vegetarian, don't eat meat.
Self-harming, that's because of all the
problems I've had.
Depression, anxiety, panic attacks.
I would just love to be a normal person.
I think I am normal.
I think my life is normal.
But sometimes I like to just come in the
gym, open the gym, just say, just talk to
one or two lads in the
gym.
Just a normal conversation and then you
get that one and go, oh, why aren't you
showing blah blah from there?
And you think, oh.
Sean Smith was an extremist who
specialised in spreading terror for no
rational gain.
But the hidden costs of this guerrilla war
haunts him to this day.
I've had these for like 20 odd years.
You know, to a lot of people they don't
mean that, but to me, they do mean a lot,
you know.
I'm the greatest King Kong.
No, you know how fucking I am.
There's me there in the suit.
I'm not the greatest, but that's just the
suit.
I'm superstitious like that.
Do you know what I mean?
It's a ritual I have every day, just
little things, you know.
Right hand for paying out, left hand for
receiving.
So I want the left-handed to have a lot of
time to receive money, have a lot of
bills.
Are you religious?
No.
Just people laughing here.
No, no.
I don't believe in God and all that.
Although I do the sign of the cross,
that's just respect for people that pass
away.
and probably a few people I'd put away
myself.
I know it's nothing to laugh about, but
that's just the life people are born into.
It's like, you know, I've just lost a
great friend of mine, John Maltz, British
champion.
champion kickboxer, world champion
kickboxer, and to go from such a powerful
man.
We watched him fade away last week and
that was like tearful.
I had to walk out, you know, I get a bit
choked on.
Just
let that one pass.
But you know what happened to the best of
people.
I have been scared of dying in the past
but I think because I've had four or five
attempts on my life and when I did get
kidnapped and
locked in a container and they were
shooting at the container and I'm ramming
the car in it I honestly thought I was
going to die that day.
I pissed myself.
I thought I'm going to fucking die here.
I didn't.
You pass that fear because the fire and
the gun and the steel container, the ram
on the car and the poor and peddling in
the sand
are going to light it.
You have this sort of feeling where you
think, I'm not going to fight, I'm going
to die.
I'll go out fucking fighting or I'll go
out roaring.
I'm not going out cowering in the corner.
You know what the lad's on with him.
He's actually on YouTube.
He put...
A gas canister on his wheelchair.
I'll show you.
And let the gas go, fired his wheelchair
along like a rocket.
Did he?
But one ran out of gas because the guy
wouldn't sell his new Fadex dignities.
He only sold the second hand ones and he
made us scratch his company logo off in
case I died.
Fucking hell I just thought, fuck it, if I
die, I die.
Since the last interview you see me with
the cut that was on my stomach.
I got out, carried on with the drugs, I
was sat in the bath, had enough,
slashed my face.
I hit the artery on my forehead, on the
side of my head here and the blood was
just squirting out.
Good job my dad was in the house, he was
sat in the bath.
The bath was just covered in blood.
Last night was a good thing for me because
I got diagnosed.
They know what the problem is with my
mental health now and everything.
It's emotional unstable personality
disorder.
I'm triggered by the child abuse.
I feel a lot more positive and more
confident that I'm going to nail it this
time.
That I'm going to beat my demons.
Alright, I've had demons for 20 years, but
I've gone to battle with them
and I've lost.
Now I've declared war on them.
I might have lost some battles, but I
ain't losing the war.
Fuck that.
I ain't going to carry these war scars for
nothing.
Luke, the boss now, he's my older brother.
He didn't speak to me for a couple of
months.
And he gave me one last chance.
It's a good way to keep me off all the
gear and shit.
I'm surrounding myself with positive
people, with a positive sport, rather than
negative dickheads with dickhead drugs.
There we go.
Don't refuse a proposition.
You will be made next week.
You will be taken on...
You'll get a nice big dent in here
tomorrow.
You will be taken on...
Fresh vitality during the next few weeks.
Few minutes, good that mate.
Getting ready for your fight.
Bit of vitality, getting ready, getting
fresh, hungry, win the belt.
Get a fresh bit of gear then.
It's not your neck it's your belt.
New Yorker number two will keep your
future fine.
Fuck off bollocks.
Right, so what I'm gonna show you here is,
remember from last time at the office,
when we had the little listeners, over
like the Steroid
22 lads.
Tony, the lad who was like, oh, I'd like
for Sean to do anything for Sean.
If you remember, jumped up in the office
and started to hit one of the lads with a
pathetic punch.
The little cockroach.
He was already selling steroids in and
around the gym, running away to me.
And then lo and behold, he come in on a
Friday morning, he's not here.
The lads have beaten the door down.
A couple of lads have gone up.
They're kicking the door in.
He's not there.
So we check our cameras and here he is
now, leaving here.
Look, here's the little cockroach now,
look at him.
Fucking blows my breath, look at that.
He's left his birds, left all his kids,
and as long as he's alright, he took no
one else's stuff on his own.
Look, look, he's having his hands, look,
he's like...
You see them on there?
That is tooting barbs.
We know there's contact with your bars
tomorrow, so we're waiting for them to
ring up and buy some more.
And then, you know, you're going to have a
bit of an accident.
Yeah, because it's not going.
I really helped that kid.
I really did help him.
And he just shit on me big time.
No, I'm having it.
This is Tony's.
This is where Tony lived and, you know, he
ran the gym for me.
This room hasn't been cleaned out yet.
You know, look at that.
You know, it's fucking disgusting.
You know, he's a personal trainer.
You know, he trains people and he's
writing people diets.
How the fuck can he live like this?
You know, it was like 87 bags of big
scattered all over the couch.
All over here, all this stuff is here,
it's just fucking junk.
It's all just a big fucking front, you
know, but that's what drugs do to
you.
This is Tony's paraphernalia that we found
upstairs.
You know, obviously he's taking stegs,
well I think it's stegs, it's a two-set
anyway, could be heroin for all I know.
And they haven't had a good look through
it to be honest.
That's a coat bag being used.
That looks like a big bag.
Look, I don't even know what they are, but
they're going in the bin.
They're going in the fucking bin.
That's barb shit.
He's just gone up and left, you know what
I mean?
He's left crappy watches.
Burn, burn.
Fucking ring going in the bin.
I hope he sees this.
Burn.
And all that fucking juice that he's paid
for.
That can go in the fucking bin as well.
But you know what?
I wouldn't give him back a fucking bottle
of fresh air.
It can go in the fucking bin.
Where it is, that's where he'll be going.
Cockroach.
Tasty?
I'll be back in a
minute.
Oh, God.
No, not just the business that I'm proper,
but I'm up to debt because my mates up
there has been had off for nearly 300
grand.
Tony's had me off for 3,500 which is a lot
of money.
Some people might think, he's got a drug
problem, give him a hand.
Well, I gave him a hand, that's why he was
there with me.
Everything was there for him.
And to get shit on and it's just,
everything's negative, you know.
It just, it affects me in every little
way.
It's like, I think, you fucking little
maggie.
Okay.
Well I should say this, there's no one
here to sort my problems out.
I have no one.
It's so fucking hard mate because people
look up to you and expect you to be there
and see all of them
crying and you know, I get fucking fed up
as well you know.
My little things is like, I would love to
have my daughter on camera and seeing a
different
side of me I don't trust people out there.
I don't want them seeing my daughter.
I don't want my wife on it either.
Everyone loves their kids and everyone's
got the best kid, but she's just an
adorable kid.
I have five daughters.
I'd love to show you me being, yeah, I let
them put a bra on my face and put bows in
your hair.
Yeah, the kids are, you know, I look
stupid, but hey, I'm just a dad, you
know.
Since filming this, Sean hit the jackpot,
landing the biggest deal of his career.
a £1 million debt in Portugal.
The payoff was a much-needed, all-expenses
holiday in the sun.
After all, going straight hadn't turned
out to be the quiet life he'd once dreamt
of.
Nat is still working with his brother.
He's clean and no longer self-harming.
He's also busy training for his pro-boxing
comeback, his last shot at the title.
Tony is still on the run.
His family fears if he comes back, he may
go on the missing list forever.